Something was messed up with it, so they
wasn't going to get here in time. Oh, so
what up?
>> So, I had to go regular.
>> [laughter]
>> Commercial? For sure.
What college? It's all good though, you
know, save some money, man.
I'm
I'm going to be doing that still, huh?
Which one? The red eye last night? Uh
no, I left this morning at like I think
it was like 6:00 something a.m. How much
sleep did you get?
Uh I slept on a plane, but I ain't sleep
before that. I since I got drafted I
ain't sleep. My friends is over at my
hotel, so we were just up in there
chilling talking, and by the time we
knew it was like, bro, it's already
3:45. We might as well just stay up. We
leaving at like 4:00 or something.
So, we tried to stay up. I was like
fighting my sleep.
So, you said? Yeah, I had a suite uh
at Resorts World. Yeah, yeah, and I was
at Resorts World uh at the Crockfords.
Yeah, so we had like the
uh
like the five-bedroom like suite in
there, so it was pretty solid. Yeah, for
sure. How many square feet is that? I
don't even know. It was crazy though.
Like I took a a tour video and I sent it
to just like my friends and stuff, and
the video was like 4 minutes. It was
like, damn, bro.
>> [laughter]
>> And I was like, bro, it's still going.
I'm like, yeah.
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah, so. Has it settled in for you yet,
or has it become real? Nah, it's become
real for sure, especially when I put my
helmet on. I'm like, whoa, like I'm
really really in NFL organization, and
they said they were going to put my
locker next to Drake, so
um
that was pretty cool, too. So, I was
like, damn, like I'm really I'm really
here. Like I came on a on the 30 visit.
Um but now like it's not a 30 visit.
Like it's my it's my spot. Um and this
is actually where I wanted to be, so I'm
pretty excited.
Why did you want Atlanta?
Really just the coaches overall. Um I
feel like they allowed me to be myself.
Um you know, and just just show my
personality and things like that. But
when it comes down to you know, handling
your business on the field, then you
know, you got to be on that. But I like
the the balance that they had with it,
and and they love football, so do I. So,
I think that's why we clicked a lot. I
honestly said that last night, too,
about how like you wanted the finest
team to love you for you. Yeah. So, like
how how do you try to explain who you
are and and
um what does that look like of a team
loving you for, you know, you? So,
really I just be myself. Um you know, I
kind of just grew up. My parents just
telling me to be yourself. Um you know,
and and and show respect and you know,
have high character and things like
that. And and treat people how you want
to be treated. Um you know, just because
I'm good at football or whatever the
case is, like we're all still human
beings. Like ain't nobody higher than
so-and-so. Like we all we all equal.
That's how I look at it. You know, I'm
just blessed with the abilities that I
do on the field. Um you know, so I kind
of just be myself, and if a team likes
me for me, um then they like me. If they
don't, I really don't care. I ain't
going to lie. Like I just want somebody
who, you know, believes in me and likes
my personality and me for myself, so
yes, sir.
All right, there was a lot said about
your route tree. What what would you say
to those people who said that you're
just a screen guy? Yeah, um you know, I
think I proved that at the combine and
pro day. Uh you know, I can run every
single route. Um I think I showed that
for sure. Um just being able to to show,
okay, certain routes I ran like a
I'm running every pretty much every
route. Um you know, curls, deep digs,
corners, comeback. Um you know, I ran a
corner that looks like it's a corner
that I ran a stop corner stop, you know,
like just being able to stop and start
on a dime is something that, you know, I
pride myself in. And I've been able to
run routes uh you know, since high
school.
Um and I feel like it I got a chance to
do that at the combine. Um you know, and
at the pro day to show people that I I
can do everything pretty much.
So, I'm excited. You had 20 reps uh 225
bench, and you weigh like 170 something.
Yeah, I'm like 180. 180? The combine I
was 177. I like threw up and all that
before weigh-in, but
>> [laughter]
>> Threw up? Yeah. I don't know. I think I
got like
>> [clears throat]
>> some food food messed my stomach up. Um
I had to start feeling weird randomly
before before I weighed in. We were
actually like in the weigh-in room.
And I was like, yeah, you got to bring
trash cans.
>> [laughter]
>> So, I lost some pounds, but yeah, I'm
180. But you still had 20 reps in you
though, you know? Yeah, I
uh
I kind of wanted to get like around 24
to 25. Cuz combine training I got like I
think the most I got was like 22.
Um so, I I imagine my adrenaline was
going to like help me out a little bit
to get 25.
Um but we was warming up. I think it was
me, Deion Burks, and another guy. We was
we was warming up. It was like, yo, why
does this 135 feel like that?
I just had to lock in. I had to get at
least 20. Um that was that was my
minimum number. Um so, I was happy that
I had a two in front of my number for
sure. And you always
>> had that like strength and athleticism
for your size? Oh, yeah, definitely. Um
you know, I power cleaned 300 in high
school. I squatted 515 in high school.
Like I've been I've been strong for a
minute. Um and I think it goes to, you
know, I do a lot of body weight stuff.
Like my dad was a high performance
strength and conditioning coach. He used
to train Serena Williams before he had
me and my brother, so he has a lot of
background of, you know, the right
training um to to get explosion and
strength at the same time. We do a lot
of endurance stuff, too. That's why I'm
able to do 20 reps. Um and then we do
like a lot of body weight stuff as kids
before we started lifting. So, today
still I do like 100 push-ups, 100
sit-ups every day just to just to stay
on my maintenance. Um and I feel like
that's like the little lockout like when
you get right here on bench, like all
those push-ups when you get right there
sticking point, like that's the ability
to be able to lock out. And my dad still
does it, too. Um like he fills up like
the little water machine at our house or
whatever. And it has like a whole cycle,
like cleans and every whatever. He's
like, watch when it cleans, I'm hitting
my push-ups. He hitting his 100 real
quick. And he trying to like time it up
before the water overflows.
But um yeah, I've always been strong.
Like even when I got to Georgia, I think
people were shocked. Like I'd be lifting
with the linemen, like D-linemen,
O-linemen. I was probably one I was
probably strongest pound for pound on
the team.
Um but they was like, damn, bro, like
you power clean 315? Like we doing that
with the linemen. I'm like, yeah, like
get your weight up, bro.
I always wonder,
guys with your athleticism, at what
point in your life did you realize you
just move different?
Definitely like five. Yeah.
Cuz I was playing flag. Like I just saw
a video. I think I posted it the other
day.
I I like was running back. I got the
ball, and I cut back like three times in
flag. And like my jersey's like all
flappy.
>> [laughter]
>> I'm like, yo, like
but like I knew I always moved
different, but like now looking back at
it,
nah, that was crazy. I ain't going to
lie. Like I move exactly the same as I
move right now, but I was 5 years old.
Um and then I had like a couple play I
like I was scoring like
average probably like at least five
touchdowns every game. Like when I was
in youth football.
And then the most I scored was I think
like eight. But one time I remember it
was a story. We played this one team
called the Gators, and they was like the
top team. It was like us and them. And
one of my uh we played them earlier in
the year. I think I had like four
touchdowns or whatever. And then um like
I was going crazy on every team, like
going whole bunch of touchdowns every
week. And then we were about to play
them again. And one of the linemen was
like, bro, I bet you don't score six
touchdowns versus us though. And he was
like, I'll give you $20 if you do. So, I
was like, all right, bet. Like watch.
And I end up scoring six touchdowns. And
then I was like, yo, like where my $20
at? And he never gave it to me.
>> [laughter]
>> And we he uh he actually went to Vegas
uh high school in Vegas, too. So, I used
to always be like, bro, like where my 20
at, [laughter] bro?
And I still never got it, but it's all
good, man. But I knew definitely that
early for sure.
How did going to a big school like
Bishop Gorman, and then going to USC,
then Georgia, like you've been at like
the biggest, most competitive schools in
the country for like your whole career.
How has that shaped you and who you are
today? Oh, yeah, definitely uh shaped me
a lot. Um real competitive. I don't like
losing. Like I just told them in the
other interview like I'm a team guy.
Like I like winning. Um that's why I
loved, you know, the transition over
there at Georgia and and the the culture
that he's emphasized. Um you know,
everything's based on winning. Like
shoot, if you got to play special teams,
you going to play special teams to help
win. So,
um I think Bishop Gorman I think I
probably lost like three times
ever at Gorman. Um
so, we didn't we weren't used to losing.
Um we ain't take losing lightly. If we
lost, we was hot. We was going to figure
something out to to try to make sure we
we didn't lose again. Um so, I always
had that competitive edge. And then
given my brother, too, like growing up
with him, we are close in age. Um you
know, shoot shoot, that's my best
friend. So, I always just grew up
competing um you know, at at little
stuff. Who can drink their shake the
fastest? Like I've always just been
competitive. Um and then going to a a
school like Bishop Gorman definitely
helped elevate that competitiveness for
sure. And then like going to USC as
well, same type of competitiveness. And
then Georgia um it it was times 1,000,
so definitely definitely wanted to get
back into an environment that was, you
know, along those competitive lines cuz
Coach Smart going to hold you to that
standard. Um and if you not on that
standard, then you know, you're forced
to elevate. And that he he going to yell
at you on that mic if you not if you not
up to par. And that forces players to be
like, I'm not trying to get that again,
so I need to be on my stuff. So,
iron sharpens iron, so I love competing,
and I don't like losing, so I definitely
think everything accumulated to to my
drive for competitiveness for sure. I
would imagine he yelled at you at some
point. Oh, yeah, definitely when I first
came, man. I got like a I was just
telling them caught a pass or whatever,
juked somebody, got like 30 yards. I
like ran out of bounds or whatever. Like
I'm in the next huddle huddle next play.
I did my first down celebration. Like I
thought I was lit. It was when I first
came, too, in the spring. I'm like,
yeah, I just popped it on them. I'm
like, first down. Like yeah, they going
to know what I'm about. He like, are you
running out of bounds? Like what are you
doing? We don't do that here.
I'm like, yo, like he he ripped me
[laughter] for sure. And then
like it would be days later. I was like,
yeah, I'm not doing that again cuz he
like he was saying some stuff for a
little minute, like a few minutes. I'm
like, coach, he still going.
>> [laughter]
>> Um and then someone else would run out
of bounds, and he'd be like, that's that
Zach Brad right there. I'm like, yo,
like I didn't even do that.
So, he was he was on me like the whole
spring about that.
Um but I definitely think that um you
know, it definitely helped the way I ran
and things like that. I always was like
a a finish strong and things like that,
finish through contact. Um and try to
get as many yards can, but I think that
helped amplify just a little bit more.
Like, all right, bet. Like, I'm going to
go truck this dude now cuz you talking
about I'm running the bounce. So, he
kind of like plays mind games to see how
you're going to react. But, I use that
as fuel. Like, all right, coach, what
what should I do next? Like, that's kind
of how I use it. Um, so I got a lot of
respect for coach Smart, for sure.
How many you take with any other top 30
visits? Uh, I just had the Raiders. A
lot of zooms, though. But, yeah, just
those two in person. Um,
I'm here like, I know that a lot of them
believe it and they get each other, but
did anything about the way that either
coach Smart, coach Cunningham spoke with
you, you know, kind of presented things
stick out to you that compared and then
comparing them to other teams?
Um, really just the overall approach.
Um, you know, I feel like it was just
pretty natural. Um, you know, sometimes
things can seem like it's forced or you
trying to force a conversation or force
a connection. Like, everything just
gelled so perfectly. Um, you know, I
felt like on the visit and then, um, you
know, from everybody, honestly. Like,
the weight room staff, the nutrition,
like, the coaches, everybody pretty much
was was real comfortable. Um, you know,
so they made me feel comfortable and and
made them or let me know that I was a
priority as well. So, um, felt very
welcoming and then, um, you know,
talking to the GM as well was had a
great conversation with him. Um, you
know, talked to him a couple times when
I came up here.
Um, you know, so so I had a real good
conversation with him and I felt really
good about the visit once I left. What
did you guys talk about? Ooh, sorry. Uh,
so we just pretty much talked about, um,
you know, how I grew up, things like
that. Um, you know, hardships and things
like that, you know, from my
perspective, his perspective. So, we had
a really good meeting. Um, you know, I
got a little bit of vulnerable up in
there. Um,
for sure, just letting them know like
what it is. Um, you know, like I said, I
try to tell people like who I am and
show who I am as a person. And if you
like it, then you like it. If you don't,
then you don't. But, I think we gelled
pretty well um and had a good
connection.
Did you get a chance to talk to him at
all? I did, actually. Um, I talked to
him actually we were on the 30 visit
together. And we always like were cool
on social media, whatever the case is.
My first time meeting him was at the
combine. Um, so it was cool to meet him
in person um and just chop it up. And
he's faith-led too, just like me. So, I
think we connect on that level as well.
And we both got the same mentality like
how we're wired. Um, and then after I
got drafted, he had text me and was
like, let's go. Like, let's turn it up.
Um, and then I had FaceTimed him like,
when you get in and stuff. I know he
came a little bit earlier this morning.
Um, but yeah, he he chopped it up with
me and we excited to go to work, for
sure.
Anything else? I don't know if you
remember, we spoke at the Sugar Bowl.
>> Yeah, we did.
Actually, all the questions that you've
been very patient with.
>> Yes, sir. One thing that's that's
striking to me and and coach Smart said
about it is that you
like you seem to treat this like, you
know, an NFL veteran does. Like, I asked
you yesterday about, you know, who else
you have on the side, your your therapy
guy and
not every college kid does that. And I'm
curious, where did that come from, that
kind of just commitment to
getting better and taking care of your
body and doing all those things that
not every college kid does. Yeah, I
think overall, um, the commitment and
consistency and discipline level that I
I approach the game with comes from just
how I was raised. Um, you know, my
parents just showed me that and whatever
you end up doing, you got to be
consistent and disciplined if you want
to be successful. And I feel like they
showed me that and you have to make
sacrifices as well. Um, you know,
sometimes you got to sacrifice things
and you got to do things that you
um
need to do in order to get what you
want. Um, so I think I I learned that
early on and I kind of just got that
like along from the athletic side, I got
that from my dad as well. Um, you know,
just him lining up the things like,
okay, if you want to actually get to
this level, here's what you need to do.
Um, you know, and given the people he's
training like Serena Serena like I'd be
dumb not to listen. Like, so uh, you
know, he he set me up in a good
position, um, you know, along those
lines and and I feel like you got to
take care of your body. You only have
one body. Um, and the best ability is
availability. So, um, I take pride in
that, take pride in my sleep, um, and
things like that cuz I feel like when I
am on the field,
uh, you know, I feel like I'm a
different breed. So, I got to just
control everything I can, um, you know,
in order to to set myself up in the best
position possible. And I think uh, found
a good routine that works for myself and
ultimately it was in Georgia already.
So, I'm just going to stick to to what
worked for me and and hopefully continue
to
to have more blessings in the future.
You guys can you guys can know earlier
about transitioning to play in the SEC.
What was it like for you coming from USC
and playing in that?
Um, Just the brand of football, I guess.
Yeah, I think
I don't know. I I feel like football
football at the end of the day, like,
it's the same game. Um,
you know, definitely
definitely I think the trenches is is
where the the big difference I feel like
is. Um, you know, we played Ole Miss. We
look at the the the scouting report. One
of them dudes was like 6'7. I said, yo.
Like, yo, that's crazy. Um, just seeing
that, but I feel like like skill-wise,
like, it wasn't really it wasn't really
nothing different for me, honestly.
Um,
but I think I think the trenches is is
something that I noticed like, yeah,
they got some they got some dudes in
them trenches. Um, you know, the
Keldrick Baughs, dudes like that. I'm
like, yo, they coming off the edge. Um,
but but it was definitely a a smooth
transition. Just Georgia allowing me to,
you know, get into the practice culture
and the way that they practice, covering
down every single time. Like, I already
did that, but like, the way that it was
amplified at Georgia, like, it made me
so consistent. Like, there would be
plays in practice where I'm just running
to the ball. Like, okay, I'm blocking
somebody, dude breaking, I'm just
running. Like, I'm just running to the
ball. That's helping with conditioning
at the same time. I can run routes. Now
I'm coming back. Like, I rarely got
tired like in a game. Like, I feel like
I could play another game after every
game, pretty much. Um, and I think that
helps with injuries as well. Um, just
being able to have like stamina. And
then, shoot, it just puts you in a good
position. Like, couple times people
would fumble in practice, I'm running to
the ball. The ball pops out, I'm right
there. Like, I I just jump on it. I
think Arian Smith did a good job with
that at Georgia, too. Just covering down
to the ball. Like, I watched a lot of
their film um, like in the offseason and
in the spring and just seeing like how
these other receivers were moving and
going about their way when they were at
Georgia. I just saw him he was a he was
a fast guy as well, track guy. Always
running. Always running. Always keep
moving to the whistle's blown. So, you
never know how that can affect the team.
And I saw a couple times in the game
where he would do that. The ball would
pop out and he's always right there and
he would save a game. Like, those are
moments where turnovers can hurt a game
bad. Um, and and just putting yourself
in those situations
um can definitely help the team. So, I
think that's really important.
All right.
Appreciate y'all. Good to see you, man.
And fun to find out your new your new
teammate right here. Okay.
Who we think?
Pick is in. Pick is in. What was the
last pick? I didn't even see it. Clark
Harris, just Kendall Daniels, linebacker
from